<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Ruboto IRB</string>
    <string name="version_name">0.7.1-dev</string>
    <string name="demo_scripts_version">15</string>

    <string name="IRB_Tab">IRB</string>
    <string name="Editor_Tab">Editor</string>
    <string name="Scripts_Tab">Scripts</string>

    <string name="Enter_source">Enter source code here.</string>
    <string name="No_scripts">No scripts loaded yet.</string>

    <string name="Menu_run">Execute</string>
    <string name="Menu_save">Save</string>
    <string name="Menu_new">New</string>
    <string name="Menu_history">Edit history</string>
    <string name="Menu_about">About</string>
    <string name="Menu_edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="Menu_delete">Delete</string>
	<string name="Menu_share">Share on Facebook</string>
    <string name="Menu_rescan">Reload scripts list</string>
    <string name="Menu_reload">Reload demos from assets</string>
    <string name="Menu_clear_irb">Clear IRB output</string>
    <string name="Menu_edit_irb">Copy IRB output to editor</string>
    <string name="Menu_max_screen">Toggle usable screen</string>
    <string name="Menu_line_numbers">Toggle line numbers</string>
    <string name="Menu_goto">Go to line number</string>
	<string name="Menu_import">Import Script</string>

    <string name="Dialog_ok">Ok</string>
    <string name="Dialog_cancel">Cancel</string>
    
    <string name="About_text">Ruboto IRB is a UI for scripting Android using the Ruby language through JRuby.
\n\n
Source code:\n
http://github.com/ruboto/ruboto-irb\n\nJoin us or give feedback:\n
http://groups.google.com/group/ruboto
\n\n
Developers:\n
Charlie Nutter\n
Jan Berkel\n
Pascal Chatterjee (jruby-for-android project)\n
Scott Moyer\n
Daniel Jackoway\n
Uwe Kubosch
\n\n
JRuby Project:\n
http://jruby.org\n\nIcon:\nRuby Visual Identity Team\n
http://rubyidentity.org\nCC ShareAlike 2.5
\n\n
Syntax highlighting though CodeMirror:
\n\n
Copyright (C) 2011 by Marijn Haverbeke &lt;marijnh@gmail.com&gt;
\n\n
Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal
in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:
\n\n
The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in
all copies or substantial portions of the Software.
\n\n
THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN
THE SOFTWARE.
\n\n
The Ruby mode for CodeMirror is provided by Ubalo:
\n\n
Copyright (c) 2011, Ubalo, Inc.\n
All rights reserved.
\n\n
Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:
\n\n
* Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.\n
* Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.\n
* Neither the name of the Ubalo, Inc. nor the names of its contributors may be used to endorse or promote products derived from this software without specific prior written permission.
\n\n
THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS "AS IS" AND
ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED
WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE
DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL UBALO, INC BE LIABLE FOR ANY
DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES
(INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES;
LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND
ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT
(INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS
SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
</string>

    <string name="Script_update_text">We have made modifications to the demos. Please update now or click cancel and update manually later.</string>

    <string name="Ruboto_remove_text">We move the core ruboto scripts into the apk. Your old ruboto scripts need to be renamed to keep them from interfering with your scripts. Press ok to rename them now or cancel to rename them later.</string>

    <string name="Update_ok">Update</string>
</resources>
